Guide to the Pierce County Central Labor Council Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Pierce County Central Labor Council records, 1890-1970; 2882-001; 30.83 cubic feet
  - PIERCE COUNTY CENTRAL LABOR COUNCIL, Records Subgroup 1
    - CORRESPONDENCE, 1913-1970; SERIES III (Box-folder 1/3-22/3)
      - Incoming Correspondence, 1913-1970; Subseries A (Box-folder 1/3-17/30)
        - Project Workers, 1936 (Box-folder 10/6)
        - Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/7)
        - O-P, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/8)
        - Retail Clerks, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/9)
        - Salmon Purse Seiners, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 10/10)
        - Shingle Weavers, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 10/11)
        - Boot and Shoe Workers, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 10/12)
        - Stage Employees, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/13)
        - State County and Municipal Employees, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 10/14)
        - Street and Electric Railway Employees, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/15)
        - R-S, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/16)
        - Tacoma, City of, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/17)
        - Tailors, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/18)
        - Teachers, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/19)
        - Teamsters, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 10/20)
        - Teamsters, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 10/21)
        - Theatrical Federation, 1935-1937 (Box-folder 10/22)
        - T, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/23)
        - Upholsterers, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/24)
        - U.S. Works Progress Administration, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/25)
        - United States government, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/26)
        - Washington State, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/27)
        - U-Y, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/28)
        - L-Y, 1940-1946 (Box-folder 10/29)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1941, 1944 (Box-folder 10/30)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1945 (Box-folder 10/31)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1946 (Box-folder 10/32)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1947 (Box-folder 11/1)
        - AFL-CIO, 1958 (Box-folder 11/2)
        - AFL-CIO (part 1 of 2), 1959 (Box-folder 11/3)
        - AFL-CIO (part 2 of 2), 1959 (Box-folder 11/4)
        - AFL-CIO (part 1 of 2), 1960 (Box-folder 11/5)
        - AFL-CIO (part 2 of 2), 1960 (Box-folder 11/6)
        - A, 1958 (Box-folder 11/7)
        - Barbers and Beauty Operators, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/8)
        - Building and Construction Trades Council, Tacoma and Pierce County, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/9)
        - Building Service Employees, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/10)
        - B, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/11)
        - Central Labor Councils, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/12)
        - Chamber of Commerce, Tacoma, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/13)
        - Citizens' Committee for School Support, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/14)
        - C, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/15)
        - Technical Engineers, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/16)
        - D-E, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/17)
        - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/18)
        - F-H, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/19)
        - Henry M. Jackson, US Senator, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/20)
        - I-L, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 11/21)
        - Machinists, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/22)
        - Warren G. Magnuson, US Senator, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/23)
        - Meat Cutters, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/1)
        - Musicians, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/2)
        - M, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 12/3)
        - Office Employees, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/4)
        - Painters, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/5)
        - N-P, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/6)
        - Religion and Labor Council of America, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/7)
        - Retail Clerks, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/8)
        - State County and Municipal Employees, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/9)
        - R-S, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/10)
        - Tacoma, City of, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/11)
        - Teachers, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/12)
        - Thor C. Tollefson, US Representative, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/13)
        - T, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/14)
        - U, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/15)
        - Waslhington State, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/16)
        - Washington State Labor Council, 1959 (Box-folder 12/17)
        - Washington State Labor Council, 1960 (Box-folder 12/18)
        - V-Y, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12/19)
        - AFL-CIO (part 1 of 2), 1961 (Box-folder 12/20)
        - AFL-CIO (part 2 of 2), 1961 (Box-folder 12/21)
        - AFL-CIO (part 1 of 2), 1962 (Box-folder 12/22)
        - AFL-CIO (part 2 of 2), 1962 (Box-folder 12/23)
        - AFL-CIO Union Label and Service Trades Department, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 12/24)
        - A, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 12/25)
        - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 12/26)
        - Barbers, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 12/27)
        - Bartenders, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 12/28)
        - Broadcast Employees and Technicians, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/1)
        - Building and Construction Trades Council, Tacoma and Pierce County, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/2)
        - B, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/3)
        - Carpenters, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/4)
        - Central Labor Councils, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/5)
        - C-D, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/6)
        - Electrical Workers, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/7)
        - Furniture Workers, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/8)
        - E-F, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/9)
        - Hotel, Motel and Restaurant Employees, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/10)
        - G-H, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/11)
        - Henry M. Jackson, US Senator, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/12)
        - I-L, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/13)
        - Machinists, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/14)
        - Warren G. Magnuson, US Senator, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/15)
        - Musicians, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/16)
        - M-N, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/17)
        - O-P, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/18)
        - Retail Clerks, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/19)
        - R, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/20)
        - State County and Municipal Employees, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/21)
        - Steel Workers, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/22)
        - S, 1962 (Box-folder 13/23)
        - Tacoma, City of, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/24)
        - Teamsters, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/25)
        - Thor C. Tollefson, US Representative, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/26)
        - T, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/27)
        - United States government, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/28)
        - U, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/29)
        - Washington State Board of Industrial Insurance Appeals, 1962 (Box-folder 13/30)
        - Washington State Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/31)
        - Washington State government, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13/32)
        - Washington State Labor Council, 1961 (Box-folder 14/1)
        - Washington State Labor Council, 1962 (Box-folder 14/2)
        - W, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 14/3)
        - AFL-CIO (part 1 of 2), 1963 (Box-folder 14/4)
        - AFL-CIO (part 2 of 2), 1963 (Box-folder 14/5)
        - AFL-CIO (part 1 of 2), 1964 (Box-folder 14/6)
        - AFL-CIO (part 2 of 2), 1964 (Box-folder 14/7)
        - A, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/8)
        - Building and Construction Trades Council, Tacoma and Pierce County, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/9)
        - Building Service Employees, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/10)
        - Central Labor Councils, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/11)
        - Citizens' Committee for School Support, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/12)
        - B-D, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/13)
        - Electrical Workers, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/14)
        - Hotel, Motel and Restaurant Employees, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/15)
        - E-H, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/16)
        - Henry M. Jackson, US Senator, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/17)
        - I-L, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/18)
        - Machinists, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/19)
        - Warren G. Magnuson, US Senator, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/20)
        - Meat Cutters, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/21)
        - Musicians, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/22)
        - M-N, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/23)
        - O-Q, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14/24)
        - Steel Workers, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 15/1)
        - R-S, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 15/2)
        - Tacoma, City of, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 15/3)
        - Teachers, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 15/4)
        - Thor C. Tollefson, US Representative, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 15/5)
        - T, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 15/6)
        - U, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 15/7)
        - Washington State government, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 15/8)
        - Washington State Labor Council, 1963 (Box-folder 15/9)
        - Washington State Labor Council, 1964 (Box-folder 15/10)
        - V-W, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 15/11)
        - AFL-CIO (part 1 of 2), 1965 (Box-folder 15/12)
        - AFL-CIO (part 2 of 2), 1965 (Box-folder 15/13)
        - AFL-CIO (part 1 of 2), 1966 (Box-folder 15/14)
        - AFL-CIO (part 2 of 2), 1966 (Box-folder 15/15)
        - Barbers and Beauticians, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 15/16)
        - Building and Construction Trades Council, Tacoma and Pierce County, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 15/17)
        - Building Service Employees, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 15/18)
        - A-B, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 15/19)
        - Central Labor Councils, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/1)
        - C, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/2)
        - Fire Fighters, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/3)
        - Furniture Workers, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/4)
        - D-F, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/5)
        - Hotel, Motel and Restaurant Employees, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/6)
        - G-I, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/7)
        - Henry M. Jackson, US Senator, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/8)
        - J-L, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/9)
        - Machinists, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/10)
        - Warren G. Magnuson, US Senator, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/11)
        - Meat Cutters, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/12)
        - Musicians, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/13)
        - M, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/14)
        - N, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/15)
        - O-P, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/16)
        - Retail Clerks, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/17)
        - R-S, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/18)
        - Tacoma, City of, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/19)
        - Teachers, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/20)
        - T, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/21)
        - U, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/22)
        - Washington State government, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/23)
        - Washington State Labor Council, 1965 (Box-folder 16/24)
        - Washington State Labor Council, 1966 (Box-folder 16/25)
        - W, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16/26)
        - AFL-CIO (part 1 of 2), 1967 (Box-folder 16/27)
        - AFL-CIO (part 2 of 2), 1967 (Box-folder 16/28)
        - AFL-CIO (part 1 of 2), 1968 (Box-folder 17/1)
        - AFL-CIO (part 2 of 2), 1968 (Box-folder 17/2)
        - Building and Construction Trades Council, Pierce County, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/3)
        - A-B, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/4)
        - Chamber of Commerce, Tacoma, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/5)
        - Communications Workers, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/6)
        - Furniture Workers, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/7)
        - C-F, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/8)
        - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/9)
        - G-L, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/10)
        - Machinists, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/11)
        - Meat Cutters, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/12)
        - Musicians, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/13)
        - Newspaper Guild, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/14)
        - M-N, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/15)
        - Painters, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/16)
        - Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/17)
        - O-P, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/18)
        - Retail Clerks, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/19)
        - Steelworkers, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/20)
        - R-S, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/21)
        - Tacoma, City of, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/22)
        - T, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/23)
        - U, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/24)
        - Washington State Labor Council, 1967 (Box-folder 17/25)
        - Washington State Labor Council, 1968 (Box-folder 17/26)
        - W-Y, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/27)
        - Miscellaneous Undated (Box-folder 17/28)
        - AFL-CIO, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 17/29)
        - Washington State Labor Council, 1970 (Box-folder 17/30)
      - Delegate Credentials, 1945-1965; Subseries B (Box-folder 18/1-18/11)
        - Delegate credentials A-Z, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 18/1)
        - Delegate credentials A-B, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 18/2)
        - Delegate credentials C, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 18/3)
        - Delegate credentials E, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 18/4)
        - Delegate credentials F, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 18/5)
        - Delegate credentials G, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 18/6)
        - Delegate credentials H, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 18/7)
        - Delegate credentials I-N, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 18/8)
        - Delegate credentials O-P, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 18/9)
        - Delegate credentials R-S, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 18/10)
        - Delegate credentials T-W, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 18/11)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1913-1965; Subseries C (Box-folder 18/12-21/11)
        - Outgoing correspondence, 1913-1914 (Box-folder 18/12)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1915 (Box-folder 18/13)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1915 (Box-folder 18/14)
        - Outgoing correspondence, 1917 (Box-folder 18/15)
        - Outgoing correspondence, 1918 (Box-folder 18/16)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 1 of 4), 1919 (Box-folder 18/17)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 2 of 4), 1919 (Box-folder 18/18)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 3 of 4), 1919 (Box-folder 18/19)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 4 of 4), 1919 (Box-folder 19/1)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 1 of 4), 1920 (Box-folder 19/2)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 2 of 4), 1920 (Box-folder 19/3)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 3 of 4), 1920 (Box-folder 19/4)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 4 of 4), 1920 (Box-folder 19/5)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 1 of 4), 1921 (Box-folder 19/6)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 2 of 4), 1921 (Box-folder 19/7)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 3 of 4), 1921 (Box-folder 19/8)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 4 of 4), 1921 (Box-folder 19/9)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1922 (Box-folder 19/10)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1922 (Box-folder 19/11)
        - Outgoing correspondence, 1923 (Box-folder 19/12)
        - Outgoing correspondence, 1924 (Box-folder 19/13)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1925 (Box-folder 20/1)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1925 (Box-folder 20/2)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1926 (Box-folder 20/3)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1926 (Box-folder 20/4)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 1 of 3), 1927 (Box-folder 20/5)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 2 of 3), 1927 (Box-folder 20/6)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 3 of 3), 1927 (Box-folder 20/7)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1928 (Box-folder 20/8)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1928 (Box-folder 20/9)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1929 (Box-folder 20/10)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1929 (Box-folder 20/11)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1930 (Box-folder 21/1)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1930 (Box-folder 21/2)
        - Outgoing correspondence, 1931 (Box-folder 21/3)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1932 (Box-folder 21/4)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1932 (Box-folder 21/5)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 1 of 3), 1933 (Box-folder 21/6)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 2 of 3), 1933 (Box-folder 21/7)
        - Outgoing correspondence (part 3 of 3), 1933 (Box-folder 21/8)
        - Outgoing correspondence, 1934 (Box-folder 21/9)
        - Outgoing correspondence, 1935-1965 (Box-folder 21/10)
        - Outgoing correspondence, Undated (Box-folder 21/11)
      - General Correspondence, 1914-1966; Subseries D (Box-folder 22/1-22/3)
        - General correspondence, 1914-1933 (Box-folder 22/1)
        - General correspondence, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 22/2)
        - General correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder 22/3)
    - MINUTES, 1890-1971; SERIES IV (Box-folder 22/4-23/14, 39/1-50/2)
      - Executive Board, 1915, undated (Box-folder 22/4)
      - Executive Board, 1918-1923 (Box-folder 47/2)
      - Executive Board, 1923-1926 (Box-folder 47/3)
      - Executive Board, 1926-1933 (Box-folder 48/1)
      - Executive Board, 1933-1937 (Box-folder 48/2)
      - Executive Board, 1938-1946 (Box-folder 49/1)
      - Executive Board, 1946-1951 (Box-folder 49/2)
      - Executive Board, 1951-1955 (Box-folder 50/1)
      - Executive Board, 1956-1960 (Box-folder 50/2)
      - Executive Board, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 51/1)
      - Executive Board, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 51/2)
      - Tacoma Trades Council, 1890-1892 (Box-folder 39/1)
      - Tacoma Trades Council, 1892-1900 (Box-folder 39/2)
      - Tacoma Trades Council, 1903-1904 (Box-folder 39/3)
      - Tacoma Trades Council, 1904-1906 (Box-folder 39/4)
      - Tacoma Trades Council, 1906-1907 (Box-folder 39/5)
      - Central Labor Council, 1907-1909 (Box-folder 40/1)
      - Central Labor Council, 1909-1911 (Box-folder 40/2)
      - Central Labor Council, 1913-1914 (Box-folder 22/5)
      - Central Labor Council, 1915 (Box-folder 22/6)
      - Central Labor Council, 1916 (Box-folder 22/7)
      - Central Labor Council, 1917 (Box-folder 22/8)
      - Central Labor Council, 1918 (Box-folder 22/9)
      - Central Labor Council, 1919 (Box-folder 22/10)
      - Central Labor Council, 1917-1919 (Box-folder 40/3)
      - Executive Board special meetings on Newsboys' strike settlement, 1920 (Box-folder 22/11)
      - Central Labor Council, 1920-1921 (Box-folder 22/12)
      - Central Labor Council, 1919-1922 (Box-folder 40/4)
      - Central Labor Council, 1922-1925 (Box-folder 41/1)
      - Central Labor Council, 1925-1929 (Box-folder 41/2)
      - Central Labor Council, 1928-1929 (Box-folder 22/13)
      - Central Labor Council, 1930-1931 (Box-folder 22/14)
      - Central Labor Council, 1932 (Box-folder 22/15)
      - Central Labor Council, 1933 (Box-folder 22/16)
      - Central Labor Council, 1934 (Box-folder 23/1)
      - Central Labor Council, 1929-1934 (Box-folder 42/1)
      - Central Labor Council, 1934-1938 (Box-folder 42/2)
      - Central Labor Council, 1938-1943 (Box-folder 43/1)
      - Central Labor Council, 1943-1946 (Box-folder 43/2)
      - Central Labor Council, 1946-1949 (Box-folder 44/1)
      - Central Labor Council, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 44/2)
      - Central Labor Council, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 45/1)
      - Central Labor Council, 1954-1956 (Box-folder 45/2)
      - Central Labor Council, 1956-1959 (Box-folder 46/1)
      - Central Labor Council, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 46/2)
      - Central Labor Council, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 47/1)
      - Organizational meeting of Joint Council of City of Tacoma Employees, 1938 (Box-folder 23/2)
      - Building Trades Council, Tacoma, 1914,1922-1923 (Box-folder 23/3)
      - Building Trades Council, Tacoma, 1928 (Box-folder 23/4)
      - Building Trades Council, Tacoma, 1929 (Box-folder 23/5)
      - Building Trades Council, Tacoma, 1930 (Box-folder 23/6)
      - Building Trades Council, Tacoma, 1931-1932 (Box-folder 23/7)
      - Meetings of Secretaries and Business Agents, 1924, 1938, Undated (Box-folder 23/8)
      - La Follette Committee, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 23/9)
      - Legislative Committee, 1937, Undated (Box-folder 23/10)
      - Political Committee, 1918 (Box-folder 23/11)
      - CLC Committees, 1915, 1963 (Box-folder 23/12)
      - Policy Board of Pacific Coast District Metal Trades Council, 1919 (Box-folder 23/13)
      - Minutes of other bodies, 1915-1967 (Box-folder 23/14)
      - Minutes of other bodies, 1915-1967 (Box-folder 23/15)
    - PIERCE COUNTY INDUSTRIAL UNION COUNCIL ROLL BOOKS, 1940-1956; SERIES V (Box-folder 23/15-23/16)
      - Delegate attendance rolls, 1940-1947 (Box-folder 23/15)
      - Delegate attendance rolls, 1948-1956 (Box-folder 23/16)
    - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1903-1968; SERIES VI (Box-folder 23/17-25/6)
      - Audit reports, 1913-1915 (Box-folder 23/17)
      - Secretary-Treasurer reports, 1914-1915 (Box-folder 23/18)
      - Journal, 1903-1907 (Box-folder 24/1)
      - Journal, 1911-1914 (Box-folder 24/2)
      - Journal, 1915-1917 (Box-folder 24/3)
      - Cash book, 1918-1921 (Box-folder 58/1)
      - Cash book, 1922-1926 (Box-folder 58/2)
      - Cash book, 1926-1929 (Box-folder 59/1)
      - Cash book, 1930-1933 (Box-folder 59/2)
      - Cash book, 1933-1937 (Box-folder 60/1)
      - Cash book, 1937-1941 (Box-folder 60/2)
      - Cash book, 1941-1945 (Box-folder 60/3)
      - Cash book, 1945-1949 (Box-folder 61/1)
      - Cash book, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 61/2)
      - Record of payments by affiliates, 1915-1917 (Box-folder 24/4)
      - Record of payments by affiliates, 1918-1920 (Box-folder 24/5)
      - Record of payments by affiliates, 1921-1938 (Box-folder 24/6)
      - Record of payments by affiliates, 1939-1946 (Box-folder 25/1)
      - Per capital tax calls, 1914-1960 (Box-folder 25/2)
      - Miscellaneous financial, 1913-1936 (Box-folder 25/3)
      - Committee reports, Undated (Box-folder 25/4)
      - AFL-CIO reports, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 25/5)
      - Washington State Labor Council reports, 1956-1968 (Box-folder 25/6)
    - LEGAL RECORDS, 1910-1967; SERIES VII (Box-folder 25/7-25/17)
      - Transcript of trial of A. J. Lamence, blacksmith, Undated (Box-folder 25/7)
      - Summons and complaint, R. V. Hoyt v. CLC officers, Undated (Box-folder 25/8)
      - Agreements, 1917-1933 (Box-folder 25/9)
      - Contracts, 1939 (Box-folder 25/10)
      - Title abstract for Labor Temple property, 1941 (Box-folder 25/11)
      - Leases, 1918-1937 (Box-folder 25/12)
      - Mortgage, 1951 (Box-folder 25/13)
      - Stock certificates, investment records, 1910-1961 (Box-folder 25/14)
      - Warranty deeds, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 25/15)
      - Court documents, 1915-1967 (Box-folder 25/16)
      - Arbitration and decision records, 1937-1962 (Box-folder 25/17)
    - REPORTS, 1913-1967; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 25/18-26/5)
      - Reports, 1919 (Box-folder 25/18)
      - Board of Trustees, 1915-1916 (Box-folder 25/19)
      - Executive Board / Committee recommendations, 1913-1964 (Box-folder 25/20)
      - Legislative Committee, 1937-1959 (Box-folder 25/21)
      - Political Committee, 1919 (Box-folder 25/22)
      - Metal Trades Council, Undated (Box-folder 26/1)
      - Standing committees, 1914-1919 (Box-folder 26/2)
      - Special committees, 1914-1959 (Box-folder 26/3)
      - Reports of other bodies, 1914-1944 (Box-folder 26/4)
      - Reports of other bodies, 1958-1967 (Box-folder 26/5)
    - RESOLUTIONS, STATEMENTS, AND WRITINGS, 1900-1968; SERIES IX (Box-folder 26/6-26/22)
      - Central Labor Council, Tacoma resolutions, 1900-1919 (Box-folder 26/6)
      - Central Labor Council, Tacoma resolutions, 1920-1964 (Box-folder 26/7)
      - Central Labor Council, Tacoma resolutions, Undated (Box-folder 26/8)
      - CLC committee resolutions, Undated (Box-folder 26/9)
      - Building Trades Council, Tacoma resolutions, Undated, 1963 (Box-folder 26/10)
      - Metal Trades Council, Tacoma resolutions, 1918-1919 (Box-folder 26/11)
      - Washington State Federation of Labor resolutions, 1917-1935 (Box-folder 26/12)
      - Resolutions of other organizations, 1908-1922 (Box-folder 26/13)
      - Resolutions of other organizations, 1934-1940 (Box-folder 26/14)